just so great to be here this is my
second dry bar
uh very exciting for me i didn't i was
worried i wasn't dry enough on the first
one
we're gonna try it out again
i know some of you know who i am
uh but i'm also aware that uh
somebody are just like hey a homeless
guy got in here
i know a homeless guy when i see one and
and you're right i'm just in here to
finish my art project
[Applause]
these are my hidey holes
i put treasures in there
you might not like my treasures
[Music]
it's good to be here you know i i live
in denver colorado and
i'm just happy to be away from my
children
love them dearly i actually have a 50
custody of of both my kids and
if you know anything
you know
that's a lot of custody
[Laughter]
if you guys ever got divorced and then
realize that maybe you just needed a
sandwich
whoopsie daisies huh
turns out it was just hungry
moving on
[Music]
thank you
thank you so much
you know i've been a comedian most of my
adult life
so for the last
16 years i've been doing 200 shows a
year and
then covert hit and i
became a homeschool
i was very teacher prepared for that
yeah i'm a comic for a reason
like sorry guys daddy can't help you
with your math homework
but if you need a good fart joke i got
you
yeah that quarantine when that first hit
you know that's uh
that's brutal i'm home with my two kids
just doing all these childhood
activities you know playing board games
and doing puzzles and
crying
we still haven't finished our puzzle
we lost interest about our 85
then board games i like playing board
games you know monopoly and everything
but uh i will definitely jack up a
monopoly game
i'm not the most delicate of peace
movers you know
you thought you had some houses
the
earthquake coming through
yeah i have my kids move to pieces and
uh i regularly kick my son's butt in
chest and that's got to be pretty
humiliating when you have to move
yourself into check
he gets me back on the video games
though
yeah i'm sure i don't have to tell you
i'm not a gamer
my parents didn't even get me a system
when i was a kid they're like you can go
to your friend's house if you want to
lose on the game you know
those fighting games my friends that
kick my butt every time well like 98
percent of time then occasionally the
right hand would just do something
amazing and
remember
every kid in the room this black jaw
like we never seen that before
you put a glitch in the game
my kids man
you know i i definitely deserve
kids you know
[Music]
someone to pass on my demented sense of
humor too
i grew up with sisters i'm the youngest
of four
and uh let me just give you a little
taste of what i went through uh was
about eleven
both of my older sisters convinced me
that there was something wrong with me
because i hadn't had my period
don't yet
them
[Music]
my oldest sister gave me a tampon she's
like you might want to take this to
school with me
and then my other sister was like if it
doesn't come in like a month you should
probably tell mom
that's why i'm a comedian okay
also when i was a kid my mom told me if
i went on a roller coaster that my head
would snap off
what kind of crappy parenting skills is
that
i didn't go on a roller coaster i was
like 30 i wore seven turtlenecks
doing loop-de-loops and the tampon fell
out
[Applause]
i don't know if this is dry enough
i feel like there's some moisture
leaking in
i'm just trying to figure out i think i
need more purple
sorry i'm easily distracted
my kids
my daughter's almost 11
and she will not shut up
like seriously this girl can talk about
anything for hours
she'll tell me details of her day that
have already been an intricate part of
like yeah i remember the chicken nuggets
i made them
[Music]
my son is 13 and
that's just you know that's just a
you know dumb boy age you know
you don't know nothing at that point
i'm
tempted to tell him about his period but
hey uh
both my kids speak japanese pretty
fluently
and they're mom's japanese that would
explain it
they did some time in a japanese prison
right
well i think it's awesome that they
speak
japanese you know my family is very
language oriented like my father speaks
13 languages
even though he speaks all those
languages i'm pretty sure he was never
able to communicate with my mom
he never learned
jackie
that's a tough language
very tonal you know
so i think it's amazing my kids speak
japanese but uh you know that definitely
makes me the odd man out
you know
the kids are coming home and i'm just
sitting there and they're just
speaking japanese i'm just
come on guys i know you're talking about
me
look i know when you're doing this
you're talking about me
i don't need rosetta stone for that one
well then just tonight okay so i got
here uh this afternoon i was walking
around checking out the town very nice
little town but uh
down with that little farmer's market is
earlier in the day there was a guy with
cerebral palsy there
which
you know that should be legal
and then i was there
but the thing is he and i were heading
in the same direction
at about the same speed
but he was like 30 yards in front of me
and we walked like that for a little
while and then people started running up
to me going you're a jerk for making fun
of that guy
[Music]
i'm just trying to buy a woven basket i
don't know
[Music]
i followed that guy for a while whatever
this is a nice way to view the town
and then he stopped and uh
he started coming back so i was like in
the lead for a while
let him deal with it you know
like walking by people oh that guy is
making fun of me
my kids man
uh
you know
this agent they're at is fine i don't
mind it but i like babies that was
always my jam
anywhere from like one month to just
under two you know
it's a good baby age
i didn't make a lot of people nervous
though you know people running up there
like didn't everybody tell you not to
shake a baby
i'm just holding them
don't tell me how to raise my kids
my kids are all very healthy and
very tough yeah
you know about like baby proof in your
house you put gates on the stairs
you put one at the bottom
did you know you also need one at the
top
if you don't put one at the top the one
at the bottom just acts as a strainer
or a colander
which maybe you didn't get the joke if i
used the wrong word that you didn't know
some people are raised with strainers
somehow
just trying to hit the whole audience
like the balcony seems like colanders
[Laughter]
you know it's cool though because you
have a gate at the bottom of the stairs
and a gate at the top of the stairs
we used to just keep the kids on the
stairs
the raisin little mountain goats
it paid off too we we go up to the rocky
mountains all the time they just run up
the mountains highlights just it's just
so majestic
beautiful specimens
i miss the stroller days you know i love
pushing my kids around the neighborhood
showing them the world you know
but the thing is when you see me coming
down the street pushing a stroller
when you look in there you're expecting
to see like
a bucket of doorknobs
[Music]
it's quite alarm when you see little
asian people
where'd you get there mister
i made them
thank you thank you
this is lot of a lot of moisture
thank you
so
you know having a disability a lot of
times people are like
you know i just think it's so
inspirational that you just you're just
out in the world that's just
you're so inspirational
i'm like well thank you that's really
nice of you but i gotta tell you
uh
i'm a little uninspired by you because
there's nothing wrong with you and you
ain't done anything
[Applause]
oh here's a tampon go on
i love it i love telling jokes it feels
good to laugh doesn't it
[Applause]
and uh
you know you guys have been such a great
crowd i actually brought you guys some
gifts i uh i have a big stack of uh
[Music]
you know i figure i'm disabled i could
just make them
who am i to be hogging all these goodies
these placards are great too not just
for parking but if you get pulled over
like oh yeah officer i know i was
speeding but did i mention
don't do that
[Music]
sorry my lawyer said i had to say that
twice
there's also a disclaimer on here it
says if you're dumb enough to use this
as a real handicap placard go for it
that's on you
[Music]
so on the way i'll grab a couple you
know i i signed them and that validates
them
this thing i'm telling you man
it's my nocturnal arm yeah
sun goes down this thing got stuff to do
i'm also pretty sure it's a sign
language interpreter
i think it's japanese
maybe a little jackie
[Laughter]
you guys remember from earlier
i feel like some of you don't get
sarcasm
this is a bad show for you
and i'm not being sarcastic
thank you
i gotta say uh
over the years you know being disabled
uh definitely gotten a lot of material
for them
very lucky that i'm able to laugh at
this stuff
because you know i've definitely gone
through some some tough times people can
be real mean
about it and i guess i never understood
why people were mean about disability
because i really think people don't
realize that the disabled community
is the largest minority group on the
planet
and it's uh because the thing is they
they pile us all together
so if you're blind get in the pile
if you're deaf
help the blind guy find the pot
if you got one leg hop on
all right i'll stop
that could be endless
whenever anybody's being mean about it
where i think they don't realize is not
only are we the largest minority group
but we're also the only minority group
that you can join at any time
you're just one bad bike ride away
red rover red rover
oh you guys are awesome thank you so
much
[Applause]
[Music]